INOK LIM

UI/UX DESIGNER / FRONT-END DEVELOPER / LEARNING DESIGNER



SKILLS

Code/Interaction:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, SVN, Git, MySQL

Graphic:

Sketch, AdobeXD, Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, InVision, Premiere Pro, After Effects

e-Learning:

WordPress, Moodle, Captivate, Articulate, Camtasia

EDUCATION

1993 - 1997

Educational Technology

Bachelor's Degree Hanyang University

2000 - 2001

Interactive Multimedia Design

Post-diploma Algonquin College

1998 - 1999

Graphic DesignCertificate

Jungang Art School

 \square

inoklim@gmail.com



https://linkedin.com/in/inoklim



778-996-9209

https://inok-lim.github.io/

PROFILE

I care about the details and enjoy transforming ideas into engaging digital experiences. I appreciate the design thinking process, especially prototyping – it helps me ensure that design ideas seamlessly translate into products that function as intended and solve users' problems.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2015 - 2023 / Sage Software Canada Ltd.

UI/UX DESIGNER & WEB DEVELOPER

I designed wireframes and interactive prototypes for web and mobile software using Sketch, Axure RP, InVision, and Figma. I ensured designs met brand standards, optimizing for diverse contexts and devices, enhancing WCAG compliance and accessibility. Additionally, I developed the front-end for the Sage ERP app using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, and managed the Design System and HTML/CSS framework library for UI consistency and efficient software development life cycle.

2014 - 2015 / Best Buy Canada

DIGITAL MEDIA DESIGNER

I planned and executed multi-channel marketing campaigns, incorporating digital advertising, email marketing, and social media promotions to fortify brand identity and complement SEO strategies. Additionally, I crafted compelling graphics, motion banners, and multimedia elements for various marketing collateral such as email newsletters, signage, brochures, and flyers.

2005 - 2014 / Pixelera Inc. & eLearnza

WEB DESIGNER & E-LEARNING DEVELOPER & WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

I generated design ideas, mock-ups, and storyboards in alignment with client objectives. Crafting user interfaces and interactions, I developed bilingual online learning courses for major clients like Starbucks, Burger King, and Health Canada. My multitasking abilities enabled the successful management of various design projects concurrently, meeting deadlines with a consistent focus on high quality and attention to detail.